Hajime Suzuki, high school sophomore.
My genre of choice is BL.
I'm currently writing a BL novel,
using the ever popular Serizawa, as my model.
It's definitely over here.
You sure? You were wrong yesterday.
Is the "Haruto Serizawa" written here, me?
Does that mean you like me, Suzuki?
It's so over.
I'm sorry!
My romantic orientation
has nothing to do with my BL hobby.
I never looked at you in that way.
I see.
Then let me read it.
That novel of yours.
Huh?
Give me the honor
of being your first reader.
This was how Serizawa began reading my novel.
Huh?
That's it?
Yeah.
I haven't written more.
Sorry, I know it's bad.
You left it at such a cliffhanger...
Wait, you think it's interesting?
Yeah.
The bottom's likable?
Is the top suave?
Totally.
And I think the bottom is adorable.
What a relief.
Thanks for the feedback.
It helps that you have such a model top.
Can't deny that.
So, when will you write the rest?
I usually write during these breaks,
or at home.
On your phone?
- Yeah.
- I see.
Then don't let me stop you. Here.
- Now?
- Yeah, now.
Okay, sure.
You're going to watch me?
Yeah. I need to know what happens next.
Right...
I can't really see your screen.
Wait, I got it. Suzuki.
Sit here.
Huh?
Then I can read over your shoulder.
Isn't it weird if I sat there?
What? No, it isn't.
Come on, don't be shy.
How's that feel?
Comfortable?
I guess...
Perfect. Now get writing
for your very first reader,
Mr. Suzuki.
[Episode 2]
- Serizawa.
- Yeah?
We definitely look strange right now.
- You think?
- Yes?
I mean, if anyone saw us...
Serizawa.
I bought whatever you asked for...
- What're you two doing?
- Lunchtime!
- Uh...
- Huh?
Suzuki? 'Sup.
Why does Serizawa have you in his clutches?
He's not "in my clutches".
We're getting along just fine.
You clearly pushed him into this.
I did not.
Right, Suzuki?
Well, I mean...
Whatever, I'm starving.
Same, let's eat.
Lunch is always the best time of day.
What did she pack today...
Woah, what a feast!
Let me see.
- Your girlfriend's cooking?
- Yup.
- Give me a bite.
- Hey!
Serizawa, I should get going...
Suzuki.
Here.
Huh?
Don't worry, I bought your share.
No, we did.
Well, I'm the one who paid.
- Don't get it twisted.
- Hah!
You and your way of stating the obvious.
That's Serizawa grammar for you.
What'll you have, Suzuki?
I bought bread and rice, so take your pick.
Then I'll take a rice ball.
Sure.
Here.
Th-Thanks.
I'll pay you back later.
Don't worry about it.
It's my treat, Mr. Suzuki.
- "Mister"?
- Serizawa!
I know, I know.
It's our secret.
- No need to show off.
- Yeah, man.
Seriously.
So, what're you having?
- Fried chicken.
- Chicken?
- Don't.
- Come on, please?
- Serizawa.
- Yeah?
Could we...
- Sure.
- How about some crab sticks?
- Not interested.
- Why am I not surprised.
What's up?
Just to make sure...
You haven't told the others
about my love for BL, right?
Yeah, of course not.
Okay, good.
I don't think they'd care though.
No, you can't. Promise you won't tell.
Okay. If you'd rather I didn't, then I won't.
It'll be our little secret.
Yeah. Thanks.
In exchange...
Come have lunch with me from now on.
Every day?
Yup. I want to read your newest updates.
Please, Mr. Suzuki?
And so,
one week passed.
What should I start with?
I got into a routine of having lunch
with the popular kids.
Suzuki, open wide.
Or more accurately, I'm being fed lunch.
How's that taste?
Good, but...
Dude, what are you doing?
My question exactly.
I knew this was weird, Serizawa.
Don't mind them.
Here, open wide.
Suzuki, what is he even making you do?
Is he blackmailing you?
If he's bothering you, tell us.
Otherwise, this selfish brat won't stop.
Don't bother him!
I'm improving Suzuki's efficiency.
It's my patented Serizawa Way.
Huh?
The Serizawa Way, is it?
Lately, I've begun to realize...
Serizawa acts weird around me.
Let's start with warm-ups.
Suzuki.
Let's partner up again.
Sure.
Suzuki!
Let's walk home together.
Uh...
I take a right here. See you tomorrow.
Suzuki, wait.
Let's trade contact info.
Yeah, something's definitely up.
Another day of Serizawa attached to my hip...
Suzuki, you asleep?
If you're awake, let's talk.
Talk?
Like, on the phone?
Or does he mean a video call?
No, no way.
What should I do?
Night, Suzuki.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Why is Serizawa so interested in me?
I wonder if I should respond...
But...
I don't know.
Good morning, Mr. Suzuki.
You scared me.
Good morning.
Morning.
You look tired.
Yeah.
I wasn't able to sleep well last night.
I ended up passing the time by reading.
So, you were awake!
Sorry, I should've responded.
What did you need?
Nothing much.
I just wanted to hear your voice.
Huh?
Oh hey, we have home economics today.
It's gonna be fun, cooking together.
Serizawa...
Yeah?
Never mind.
Suzuki? Hey, wait up!
Today we'll be making
stewed chicken and vegetables.
- A stew...
- That's right.
You got all the ingredients?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Great.
Then let's get cooking.
Serizawa?
Suzuki.
I'm a heroic sort of top, right?
Huh?
I mean,
you are in my mind.
And in my mind,
most tops are great cooks.
I agree with you there.
All right then. Leave it to me, Suzuki.
I'm going to be the King of Stewing!
Huh?
What are you talking about?
I'm going to be the Stewing King.
You haven't managed to shape one?
It's been minutes.
Meanwhile, look at Takeuchi's plate.
- It's simple.
- He's so speedy.
- Like a pro.
- Woah.
I'm more impressed by Serizawa's disaster.
There.
You didn't manage to make a single slice.
We don't even need green onion.
- Huh?
- It's not called for in the recipe.
Then why'd you bring one?
- Huh?
- Dude.
Like a pencil.
This guy cannot cook for his life.
"King of Stewing", my butt.
I'll take over, Serizawa.
You've got a ways to go, man.
Yeah, about 3,000 miles left, I'd say.
- He slumped down.
- You made him depressed.
Aren't you going to become the King of Stewing?
- Come on!
- Don't give up now!
Stand, Serizawa!
- Give up on that carrot, though.
- Yeah...
Give your meals a try. Bon appétit!
Bon appétit!
Let's see how it tastes.
- Everyone got their chopsticks?
- Yeah.
That's good.
Yeah, Suzuki's stock is really flavorful.
And Suzuki's carrots
were cut to perfection.
I'm glad our group had Suzuki to help.
Yeah.
Agreed.
If you three keep complaining,
then our group's gonna split.
Sounds good to me.
I wasn't ever a part of any group.
You're our weak link anyway.
Saeki, come here.
- Koharu's stew is seriously good.
- Ignore them.
- Trust us.
- Nope, don't.
- Let me try.
- Stop it!
- Why not?
- Bon appétit!
Guys, I said don't!
You three weren't invited!
Sorry, Suzuki.
What?
I'm supposed to be a heroic top,
yet I can't even cook.
Don't let it bother you.
But I wanted to become the ideal top.
Well...
You can practice.
Huh?
I mean, not every top starts out perfect.
Really?
You think I can become the King of Stewing?
Yeah, I do.
So, don't be so down.
Okay?
Sorry! I didn't mean to act so patronizing!
You weren't.
Thanks.
I feel much better now.
You do?
Then I'm glad it worked.
Hey, let's take a selfie together.
- A selfie?
- Yeah.
Get our cooking in the picture, too.
You sure?
Yeah. Now smile!
Say cheese!
Let me get another one.
Ready?
Say cheese!
Cooking together was fun,
but it's too bad I couldn't read
your newest update today.
Oh, right.
I should've known.
Thanks for cheering me up today!
I'm going to become the King of Stewing!
I'm not the one
Serizawa is interested in.
Can't wait to read
more of your novel tomorrow!
[Plot Journal]
Suzuki. Let's walk home together.
Yeah.
Serizawa.
What's up?
There's something I need to tell you.
Okay.
Serizawa.
I'm sorry.
Huh? What's up?
The novel you're reading right now.
I probably won't ever finish it.
What?
To tell you the truth...
[Plot Journal]
I've never managed to finish a novel.
Not a single one.
When I write alone,
I get lost somewhere along the way.
I never know if my writing is interesting,
and I tend to give up before I finish.
So, if I lose heart on this work as well,
I'd feel bad about leaving you hanging.
Serizawa.
I'm not worthy of your respect at all.
What, that's it?
Huh?
You had me spooked.
I thought my cooking was so bad,
you became disillusioned with me as a top.
What?
If anything,
I respect you even more now.
I mean, you never gave up, right?
No matter how many times you lost heart,
you still continued to write.
That's seriously amazing, you know?
Besides.
You're not writing alone now.
What?
Suzuki.
If you ever get lost in your writing,
talk to me about it.
I'll come to help, no matter where I am.
I'll tell you everything
I like about your writing,
until it's hammered into your head, okay?
Serizawa...
Pinky promise.
In the meantime, I'll work hard
on becoming the King of Stewing.
You were serious about that?
Of course.
And this picture proves it.
Hey! Delete that!
Not happening.
You're being selfish again.
- Stop!
- Suzuki?
Something up, Matsuno?
Hey, isn't that Suzuki?
And Serizawa.
Why's Suzuki hanging out with him?
Just delete it.
- Delete it.
- Nope.
- Nuh-uh.
Come on, please?
Nope.
Suzupi, how'd you get so close
with Serizawa's group?
There you are.
Join us for karaoke.
I've never sung in front of other people.
Seriously?
I think I can sing.
Sorry, never mind!